<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tech Desk</string>
    <string name="Title_Main">How May We Assist You?</string>
    <string name="Title_FAQ">What Device/Service are you having trouble with?</string>
    <string name="b1">Contact Tech Desk</string>
    <string name="b2">Frequently Asked Questions</string>
    <string name="b3">About the App</string>
    <string name="f1">Wi-Fi</string>
    <string name="f2">Laptop/Chromebook</string>
    <string name="f3">Projector/Audio Connection</string>
    <string name="f4">Back to Main Menu</string>
    <string name="paragraph">
        We are a group of students from West Windsor-Plainsboro High School South looking to enhance
        the technological literacy of our community by lending a hand to whomever is in need of tech
        help. The Tech Desk operates in the Media Center throughout the day, including lunch and
        even after school while the library is open. Other than simply showing up to the library,
        volunteers are proactive in helping peers, including other library volunteers. Occasionally,
        the club partners with other clubs to build websites and holds workshops with new gadgets to
        be tinkered with. With programming and the internet in general so prevalent today,
        especially now that more students have access to technology through chromebooks in their
        daily lives, the HSS Tech Desk aims to dispel any technological doubts anyone may have.
        The HSS Tech Desk is actively involved in the school community, actively developing sites
        for fellow student-run organizations or even the district itself. More projects to be added later!
    </string>
    <string name="wifi_help">
        <b>Wifi Issues</b>

        \n\n\n1. Make sure the wifi network is up - try connecting from your phone or asking a friend if the wifi is up for them!
        \n\n2. Now that we know that the problem is on your end, make sure that airplane mode is turned off and that wifi is turned on.
        \n\n3. If you still can\'t connect, try restarting your phone and repeating steps 1 and 2.
        \n\n4. Try contacting your local Tech Team Member at the High School South Technology Help Desk (in the library) and ask for a certificate for the wifi.
        Alternatively, try installing a vpn such as x-vpn before coming to school.
        \n\n5. Your phone may be broken - try connecting to your home network; if you cannot connect to that, then you may be in need of a new phone.
    </string>
    <string name="laptop_chromebook_help">
        <b>Laptop Issues</b>
        \n\n\n1. Make sure the wifi network is up - try connecting from your phone or asking a friend if the wifi is up for them!
        \n\n2. Now that we know that the problem is on your end, make sure that airplane mode is turned off and that wifi is turned on.
        \n\n3. If you still can\'t connect, try restarting your phone and repeating steps 1 and 2.\n\n\n\n

        <h3><b>Chromebook Issues</b></h3>
        \n\n\n1. Make sure the wifi network is up - try connecting from your phone or asking a friend if the wifi is up for them!
        \n\n2. Now that we know that the problem is on your end, make sure that airplane mode is turned off and that wifi is turned on.
        \n\n3. If you still can\'t connect, try restarting your phone and repeating steps 1 and 2.
    </string>
</resources>
